DAVID YASSEIR CLEAN MOSQUERA VASQUEZ

Sound Engineer - Acoustic Designer

CONTACT cleno291@gmail.com +57 3187154699 Cali - Colombia LANGUAGE English Spanish EXPERTISE Flowstone Arduino Autocad Comsol Multiphysics **Ease Acoustics** Rhinoceros 3D

First place on Sound for audiovisual media. 2th recording and mixing competition AES

(Audio Engineering Society)

AWARDS

PROFILE

Creative and talented sound engineer with experience in acoustic design for architectural spaces and industrial noise control. Throughout his career he has provided effective development in 3D acoustic simulations and professional audio requirements. He has confidence in his ability to create ambitious ideas focused on aesthetic and efficient results.

EXPERIENCE

Seven productions — Sound Director

August 2009 - February 2010

- Live show Voices recording.
- Sound amplification for the TV stage.
- Post production of audio files

Visound S.A.S. — Internship

August 2014 - February 2015

- Design and to develop interactive audio solutions.
- Technical support for sells and projects.

Acustica Integrada Ltda. — Projects Engineer November 2015 - Present

- Projects management
- Design and develop acoustic solutions for architectural spaces
- Design and develop acoustic solutions for industrial noise
- Audio professional consultant
- Acoustic simulations
- Acoustic products design
- Acoustic measurements (laboratory/in-situ)

EDUCATION

Industrial technical institute INEM Jorge Isaac de Cali

— Metalworking approach March 2009, Santiago de Cali

Colombian Communication Institute ICC de Cali

— Sound and audiovisual technical June 2010, Santiago de Cali

University of San Buenaventura Bogota

Sound engineeringOctober 2015, Bogota DC.

"Make it simple, but significant." -Don Draper